Well, hello everyone and welcome to a
那么，大家好，欢迎来到
Englishspeaking video. I'm going to do
英语视频。我要做
something a little bit different today.
今天有些不同。
I'm just going to have a straightup
我只是要直截了当
conversation with you and I'm not going
和你谈话，我不会去
to put any subtitles. You can simply
添加任何字幕。您可以简单地
listen and in the comments you can share
聆听并在评论中分享
what new vocabulary you heard, any new
你听到了什么新词汇，有什么新的
sentences or phrase that you thought
你想到的句子或短语
were useful or some new things that
有用或一些新东西
you'd like to learn or didn't
你想学还是不想学
understand. Now, today I'm going to just
理解。现在，今天我要
talk about some recent updates in my
谈谈我最近的一些更新
life and uh I hope you enjoy it. So,
生活，呃，我希望你喜欢它。所以，
first of all, if you didn't know
首先，如果你不知道
already, I am a full-time content
已经，我是一名全职内容
creator. That means I make content on
创造者。这意味着我的内容是
all different social media platforms. I
所有不同的社交媒体平台。我
have multiple accounts. My main one is
拥有多个帐户。我的主要是
my English teaching account and my
我的英语教学帐户和我的
second one is my more comedy
第二个是我的喜剧
lifestyle vlogging account. So, I
生活方式视频博客帐户。所以，我
started doing that one recently, my
最近开始做那个，我的
second account. And I got to say it's
第二个帐户。我必须说这是
been really interesting.
真的很有趣。
I think that in life you have to
我认为生活中你必须
challenge yourself. You have to give
挑战自己。你必须给予
yourself like big goals. You need to mix
你自己喜欢大目标。你需要混合
it up once in a while. I think that when
偶尔起来一次。我认为当
you're not being challenged every day,
你并不是每天都面临挑战，
when you're not learning something new,
当你没有学习新东西时
you're not growing. And as you can see,
你没有成长。正如你所看到的，
my my my main account, my English
我我我的主账户，我的英语
accounts, they're quite popular. uh
帐户，它们很受欢迎。呃
million followers on each platform and
各平台百万粉丝
great engagement, great numbers. My
参与度高，人数多。我的
second account has been really
第二个账户已经真的
challenging. It's not getting exactly
具有挑战性的。还没有完全明白
the numbers I'd like to see. It doesn't
我想看到的数字。事实并非如此
get that instant gratification of big
立即获得大的满足感
viral numbers, big viral hits, and it's
病毒式传播的数量，巨大的病毒式传播，而且它是
been very, what's the right word? It's
非常，什么词是正确的？它是
been very um
非常嗯
humbling.
谦卑。
So by humbling I mean that it's it's
所以我说的谦卑是指就是这样
been very
非常
uh humbling to start from the beginning
嗯，从头开始感到羞耻
again to feel that feeling of failure to
再次感受到失败的感觉
kind of feel like oh man like do I suck?
有点像天哪，我很烂吗？
Do people not like me? Do do people not
人们不喜欢我吗？人们不做吗
care about what I'm saying or doing? But
关心我说的话或做的事吗？但
I'm very grateful for the opportunity.
我非常感谢有这个机会。
In a sense it is kind of lit a fire
从某种意义上说，它有点点燃了一把火
under my my uh my my butt. Sorry, I
在我的我的呃我的屁股下。对不起，我
can't curse in these videos. And it's
不能在这些视频中咒骂。这是
really
真的
encouraged me to kind of really work
鼓励我真正工作
harder than I have before. And also, I
比我以前更难。还有，我
feel that it's kind of challenged me to
感觉这有点挑战我
be more disciplined, to really think
更加自律，真正思考
outside the box, to really up my game in
跳出框框，真正提高我的游戏水平
a lot of different ways.
有很多不同的方式。
So, I feel like overall this new
所以，我觉得总体来说这个新
challenge is making me a better content
挑战让我获得更好的内容
creator in in in all different aspects.
创造者在各个方面。
For example, script writing, editing,
例如，剧本创作、剪辑、
um just just just everything because now
嗯，只是一切，因为现在
I'm trying new things and I'm looking at
我正在尝试新事物并且正在寻找
things from different angles. I I'm
从不同角度看事物。我我是
doing research and so yeah, that's been
做研究，所以是的，那就是
an interesting uh challenge for me in my
对我来说这是一个有趣的挑战
recent life. Now, the funny observation
最近的生活。现在，有趣的观察
I've seen is that a lot of comedy
我看过很多喜剧
accounts, this is really funny. So, you
账户，这真的很有趣。那么，你
know, sometimes you'll watch like a a
你知道，有时你会像一个
really viral video, like a meme or
真正病毒式传播的视频，例如模因或
something like that, and then you'll you
类似的事情，然后你就会
you'll you'll see it and you say, "Wow,
你会看到它，然后你会说：“哇，
that that that was really original."
那真的是原创的。”
Right? The thing is, when I started
正确的？问题是，当我开始
doing research on like these funny viral
对这些有趣的病毒进行研究
videos, I've noticed, wait a minute,
视频，我注意到了，等一下，
this person's doing that video as well.
这个人也在制作那个视频。
that person's doing that video as well.
那个人也在制作那个视频。
Seems like everybody's doing the same
似乎每个人都在做同样的事情
video. And so it makes you wonder all
视频。所以这让你想知道一切
these comedy accounts,
这些喜剧账户，
are any of them really original or is it
它们中的任何一个都是真正原创的吗？
more so like, okay, that person did it
更像是，好吧，那个人做到了
better, that person did it better. In
更好，那个人做得更好。在
fact, some videos I've read in the
事实上，我在网上读过一些视频
comments, they say, "Oh, you were the
评论时，他们说：“哦，你是
original, but this person did it better.
原创，但是这个人做得更好。
They at this person, this person won the
他们在这个人身上，这个人赢得了
trend." So, it's funny. It it it makes
趋势。”所以，这很有趣。它使得
me think about, you know, originality,
我想到，你知道，原创性，
you know, content creation ideas. For
你知道，内容创作想法。为了
me, I I'm I'm really proud of myself
我，我，我真的为自己感到骄傲
because honestly,
因为老实说，
I I can say to you, and I mean this, I'm
我我可以对你说，我的意思是，我
not trying to brag, for my English
不是想吹嘘我的英语
teaching content, my my my second comedy
教学内容，我我我的第二部喜剧
account,
帐户，
I try my best to not copy anybody. In
我尽力不模仿任何人。在
fact, this is the reason why I don't
事实上，这就是我不这样做的原因
even watch social media. I I rarely do.
甚至观看社交媒体。我很少这样做。
I don't scroll through videos because I
我不会滚动浏览视频，因为我
don't want to indirectly
不想间接
copy someone, you know? I don't want to
抄袭某人，你知道吗？我不想
be like, "Oh, that's a good idea. Maybe
就像，“哦，这是个好主意。也许
I should copy it." Now, I'm not going to
我应该复制它。”现在，我不打算
pretend that I'm everything is original.
假装我的一切都是原创的。
Right? Sometimes I do see something
正确的？有时我确实看到一些东西
that's really amazing, but I do try my
这真是太棒了，但我确实尝试了
best to rewrite the script and kind of
最好重写脚本和类型
make sure okay if if if the end result
确保最终结果可以
is going to be this way, the way towards
将会是这样，走向
there could be a little bit different.
可能会有一点不同。
Okay, so that kind of begs the question,
好吧，这就引出了一个问题，
you know, that and if you're still here,
你知道，如果你还在这里，
I appreciate it. It begs the question
我很感激。这就引出了一个问题
for me a as a content creator. I'm
对于我来说，作为一名内容创作者。我是
always curious about what do my viewers
总是好奇我的观众在做什么
want?
想？
What do you like watching?
你喜欢看什么？
Could you let me know like my videos?
喜欢我的视频可以告诉我吗？
Why do you watch my videos? What's the
你为什么看我的视频？什么是
appeal? Why do you enjoy them? Why do
上诉？你为什么喜欢它们？为什么这样做
you binge watch them? Hopefully,
你狂看他们吗？希望，
why do you like me? What is it about my
你为什么喜欢我？我的是什么
content that you like? You know, there
你喜欢的内容？你知道，那里
are so many other content creators. I
还有很多其他内容创作者。我
think if I were to put some words in
想想我是否要加入一些词
your mouth, I think one thing for me I
你的嘴，我想对我来说有一件事
can confidently say is that I do feel
可以自信地说我确实感觉到
that I am quite original and I really
我很原创而且我真的
try to make my English lessons fun. You
努力让我的英语课变得有趣。你
know, I could be very serious like,
我知道，我可能会很严肃，比如
okay, today we're going to learn about
好的，今天我们要学习的是
grammar. Today we're going to learn some
语法。今天我们要学习一些
advanced vocabulary, this, this, this,
高级词汇，这个，这个，这个，
that, that. But I feel, at least for me,
那个，那个。但我觉得，至少对我来说，
that
那
learning is more interesting. It's
学习更有趣。它是
easier when it's fun.
有趣的时候更容易。
You know, when you're having a good
你知道，当你过得好的时候
time, things get easier. And so, this is
时间，事情会变得更容易。所以，这是
why I try to avoid being too serious in
为什么我尽量避免过于严肃
my English lessons. This is why I really
我的英语课。这就是为什么我真的
try my best to make things fun and
尽力让事情变得有趣并且
interesting. And so that also includes
有趣的。所以这还包括
improving my acting skills, uh putting
提高我的演技，呃推杆
more comedy in my skits, uh really
我的短剧里有更多喜剧，呃，真的
putting in that extra effort. So I would
付出额外的努力。所以我会
love for you to give your feedback to me
喜欢你给我反馈
as well. You know, like I told you
以及。你知道，就像我告诉你的
before, I'm trying new things. I am
之前，我正在尝试新事物。我是
trying to step out of my comfort zone.
试图走出我的舒适区。
I'm really trying my best to really grow
我真的很努力地成长
as a content creator. I think this year
作为内容创作者。我想今年
especially,
尤其，
I've made a lot of big leaps and bounds
我已经取得了很多巨大的飞跃
in my career and I feel right now I'm in
在我的职业生涯中，我感觉现在我处于
a good spot. I feel right now the sky is
一个好地方。我感觉现在的天空
the limit. I I've been doing this for a
极限。我这样做已经有一段时间了
long time, you know, over 10 or 15
很长一段时间，你知道，超过 10 或 15
years, but it it really wasn't until a
几年了，但直到
few years ago that I started to see some
几年前我开始看到一些
real success.
真正的成功。
Thankfully, right now I'm in a good spot
谢天谢地，现在我处于一个好位置
where
在哪里
the harder I work, I'm guaranteed a
我越努力，我就保证
result. The problem is as I'm getting
结果。问题是我得到的
older, I'm not that old, but you know,
年纪大了，我没那么老，但你知道，
as I'm getting to middle age,
当我步入中年时，
I'm finding I want to do more. I want to
我发现我想做更多。我想要
do so much more, but at the end of the
做了很多事情，但最后
day, I'm tired. I want to take a break.
一天，我累了。我想休息一下。
I don't have that that urge like that
我没有那样的冲动
that fire that I did when I was in my
我在我的时候所做的那把火
early 20s anymore.
20岁出头了。
So I don't know if this is being too
所以我不知道这是否太
comfortable because I am successful or
舒服是因为我成功了或者
is it just laziness? Is it just
这只是懒惰吗？难道只是
procrastination?
拖延？
Is it just I don't have that fire like I
难道只是我没有我那样的火
used to. So again that's why I've been
习惯了。这就是我一直以来的原因
trying to step out of my comfort zone.
试图走出我的舒适区。
Do new things. This is a new thing.
做新事。这是一个新事物。
Talking to you like this, you know, in
像这样跟你说话，你知道，在
public, doing this long form video is is
公开，制作这个长视频是
something new as well.
还有一些新东西。
So, I guess that the the point of what
所以，我想这是什么意思
I'm trying to say is that I'm on a great
我想说的是我过得很好
journey right now and I'm very happy to
现在就去旅行，我很高兴
have you here with me along for the
你和我一起去吗
ride. And I do want to thank you all for
骑。我确实想感谢你们所有人
your support and I do want to thank you
你的支持，我真的想感谢你
all for really commenting, engaging my
一切都是为了真正的评论，吸引我的
content. You know, I get so many
内容。你知道，我得到了很多
comments. I wish I could respond to all
评论。我希望我能回应所有
of you, but I can't. But I do want to
你，但我不能。但我确实想要
take the time to say in this video,
花点时间在这个视频中说，
thank you so much for everything. And I
非常感谢你所做的一切。而我
love you. I really do. Without your
爱你。我真的这么做。没有你的
support, I wouldn't be here right now
支持，我现在不会在这里
doing this and making a living out of
这样做并以此谋生
doing content. Okay. So, anyways, my
做内容。好的。所以，无论如何，我的
friends, that's the end of this video,
朋友们，本期视频到此结束
but I would like you in the comments,
但我希望你在评论中，
what do you think about this type of
你对这种类型有什么看法
content?
内容？
Did you learn any new words or phrases?
你学到了什么新单词或短语吗？
What was useful for you? I would like
什么对你有用？我想
you to please tell me in the comments
请在评论中告诉我
and and also too if you understood
如果你明白的话
everything share your thoughts. How
一切都分享你的想法。如何
could I do things better? You know, how
我可以做得更好吗？你知道，如何
could I motivate myself more? How could
我可以更加激励自己吗？怎么可能
I improve? How could I stay more
我进步了？我怎样才能留下更多
disciplined? Share your thoughts with me
有纪律吗？与我分享你的想法
in the comments. And if this is your
在评论中。如果这是你的
first time here, thank you so much.
第一次来这里，非常感谢。
Don't forget to like, subscribe, and
别忘了点赞、订阅和
follow. And I will see you next time.
跟随。下次再见。
Bye.
再见。